bermudasun.bm 2013-12-21

# Bermuda Sun: Privacy Policy

## Bermuda Sun Website Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on BermudaSun.bm, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or place an order.

When registering or ordering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To process transactions
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product or service requested.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order, or enter, submit or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your credit card information will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

**Third party links**

We include third-party advertising on our website. Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online privacy policy only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms of Service**

Please also visit our [Terms of Service page](http://bermudasun.bm/main.asp?SectionID=81&SubSectionID=853) establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

**Your consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using our [Contact Us page](http://bermudasun.bm/main.asp?SectionID=81&SubSectionID=227) or via mail or email at:

Bermuda Sun Ltd  
PO Box HM 1241  
Hamilton HM FX  
Bermuda
